I'm sorry, ma'am.
They forced me to do it.
Please, just let me see her.
I want to apologize to her in person.
I'm sorry.
You misunderstood.
Back then, I...
I... Anyway,
it's not what you think.
Why are you still making excuses?
Liu Yang,
stop putting on your good guy persona.
Deep down, you're no different from them.
Except you're just
a bit more despicable.
You Psycho!
Liu Yang! Liu Yang!
To think I wanted to help you! Calm down!
She still has your child!
Bullshit! That's not my child!
You're crazy!
Stop fighting!
Are you satisfied?
Of course.
It's a live broadcast.
Xiaochen and Xiao Yu will finally get
the full picture of their parents.
Lin Yajing.
You can beat or curse at me all you want,
but can you tell me where the kids are?
You want to know?
The address.
Don't move.
Stand up.
Stop! Leave me alone!
Come over here.
Do you hear me?
Leave me alone!
I'm going to kill him!
Hurry up and take your clothes off.
Hurry up.
We said we don't want you
wearing the same uniform as us.
Move it! What are you doing?
Come on, hurry up.
So slow.
Don't touch me!
What?
Don't touch me! Okay! Wait, wait, wait!
You choose.
Either I tell those three to turn around
and you take it off yourself,
or the three of them come at you
and take it off for you. Alright?
What's your choice?
I'll take it off myself.
Okay.
Turn around. Turn, turn, turn.
You, come here.
I'm begging you.
I love that look on your face.
It's so amusing.
Who would've thought?
Such a perfectly good leg.
Your leg...
You're not crippled now, are you?
How did it end up crippled?
Does it hurt?
What are you doing?
Just showing I care. Don't move.
Tell me, does it hurt?
Gao Wenhao.
Xiao Hu, hurry to the address I gave you.
Go pick up the kid. Hurry!
Mr. Gao, we're here.
We're here, we're here.
Mr. Gao, we found Xiaochen.
She's with Xiao Yu.
Yes, perfectly safe.
Uncle Hu, what are you doing here?
Okay, okay.
Slow down. Eat slowly, there's no rush.
No one's fighting you for it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry.
You didn't do anything wrong.
No need to apologize.
Then am I a good person?
You are.
That's good.
Good things happen to good people.
By the way, who are you?
I'm your daughter.
You're my daughter.
Then I'm your mom.
Am I a good mom?
If I do something wrong,
you can just scold me.
Once I correct it,
I'll be a good mom.
I want to be a good mom.
I want to be a mom who loves to smile.
A good "Mom is the Best in the World" mom.
How have you been the last few days?
Pretty good.
Are you happy?
Teacher.
They say summer camp turns us into adults.
Is that true?
Have you ever been to one?
I have.
It's just that...
it might be a bit different from yours.
When I grow up,
I want to be someone like Teacher Yang.
Someone like me?
I want to be...
someone gentle and kind like Teacher Yang.
Did you bring your Switch?
I did.
Let's play a racing game.
Sure.